// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which ocean surrounds Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Indian Ocean",
    options: [
        "Pacific Ocean",
        "Atlantic Ocean",
        "Indian Ocean",
        "Arctic Ocean"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which ancient rock fortress is a UNESCO World Heritage Site located in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Sigiriya",
    options: [
        "Polonnaruwa",
        "Sigiriya",
        "Anuradhapura",
        "Dambulla"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Rupee",
    options: [
        "Taka",
        "Rupiah",
        "Rupee",
        "Peso"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which coastal city in Sri Lanka is for its beautiful beaches and surfing opportunities?",
    answer: "Arugam Bay",
    options: [
        "Arugam Bay",
        "Trincomalee",
        "Negombo",
        "Bentota"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which month Esala Perahera festival is celebrated in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "August",
    options: [
        "August",
        "January",
        "December",
        "November"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "In which city is the Dutch fort situated?",
    answer: "Galle",
    options: [
        "Colombo",
        "Kandy",
        "Galle",
        "Jaffna"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name of the world's oldest tree planted by humans in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Bodhi Tree",
    options: [
        "Banyan Tree",
        "Baobab Tree",
        "Bodhi Tree",
        "Sequoia Tree"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the traditional Sinhalese New Year celebration called?",
    answer: "Avurudu (Aluth Avurudu)",
    options: [
        "Deepavali",
        "Avurudu (Aluth Avurudu)",
        "Thai Pongal",
        "Vesak"
    ]
}, {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which traditional dance form of Sri Lanka features dancers wearing elaborate masks and costumes?",
    answer: "Devil Dance",
    options: [
        "Kandyan Dance",
        "Baila Dance",
        "Devil Dance",
        "Kolam Dance"
    ]
}, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the largest national park in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Wilpattu National Park",
    options: [
        "Minneriya National Park",
        "Horton Plains National Park",
        "Wilpattu National Park",
        "Wasgamuwa National Park"
    ]
},
];